Mitchell **Poco**

Software Developer

Address La Quinta, CA, 92253 Phone (610) 772-0857 E-mail pocomitch@gmail.com

LinkedIn https://www.linkedin.com/in/mitchellpoco/

Ambitious developer bringing unmatched attention to detail and unwavering commitment to the creation and maintenance of responsive fullstack applications. Independently crafted several fully-featured apps from inception to completion. Foundational grasp of HTML, CSS, Javascript, React, Node.js, Express.js, and MongoDB. Exceptionally quick learner, competent in Linux and Windows.

Independent Projects

Completed using Bootstrap, Reactstrap, Mongoose, Passport.js, Git, Postman, Bash, SSH, Amazon Web Services, and several Javascript libraries. https://github.com/scribeguru

https://wearymuser.com - Responsive blog website with chronological pagination and archive access enabled using array position and/or custom query parameter object property depending on how user chooses to interact. Dual entry management structure ties into itself, facilitating reliable dynamic styling and consistent user experience. Articles rendered using two "root" divs for title and body, optimizing application performance without sacrificing SEO to the same degree as a full SPA. Includes dynamically generated open graph meta tags for social media presence, and an email notification subscription system.

https://rockstarelite.xyz - Responsive workout assembling application allows multiple users to create and track custom exercise data through time. Uses a series of draggable user-generated forms which actively persist inputted details until logout. Dynamically provides intuitive instruction to new users, displays most recent bodyweight in their preferred measurement system, allows exercises to be clustered into a named workout for easy access, and tracks sessions in a database store in combination with Passport's local authentication scheme for security.

<u>https://mitchpo.co</u> - Responsive portfolio website, built in React.

Education

2021-03 - 2021-09

Fullstack Web And Mobile Software Development

Nucamp Coding Bootcamp - Indio, CA

Mastery of Bootcamp Curriculum

Work History

2019-04 - 2021-02

US Marine

United States Marine Corps

Led and performed as fire team member for situational training exercises and infantry dismounted battle drills. (Flourishes under pressure.)

2018-08 - 2019-

02

Restaurant Manager

Aurora Pizzeria & Pasta Kitchen, West Grove, PA

 Reduced process bottlenecks by training and coaching employees on practices, procedures and performance strategies. (Can juggle multiple problems, team player.)